ELI HORNE ME@ELIHORNE.COM

Skills

I take ideas from low fidelity concepts to polished experiences. My process includes user research, design iteration and prototyping. I also like working with video, photography and good stories.

Expert knowledge in mobile design (iOS and Android), emerging markets and productivity tools. Strong technical skills with HTML, CSS and JS.

Experience

Google

2017 - 2010

Senior Product Designer

I was a design lead for G Suite. I led Google Docs, Sheets & Forms and I contributed features to Slides. During my last year on the team I explored emerging markets and experimental editors.

OTHER CONTRIBUTIONS:

- Hangouts Meet (video chat)
- Personalization services for YouTube and G+
- Google Programmable Ads (formerly Teracent)
- Spoke at Future of Web Design on behalf of Google

Scripps Networks 2010 - 2008 Product Developer

I was a front end lead for the relaunches of HGTV.com and FoodNetwork.com. We moved the properties to a grided system and created reusable components from the related properties to share.

OTHER CONTRIBUTIONS:

- Managed all blogs for HGTV and Food Network.
- Launched Food2.com built entirely on Facebook Connect

Playboy 2008 - 2007 Visual Designer

I designed non-nude digital editorial features like "Rock the Rabbit." I went to the parties but I never got to meet Hef.

Education

College Temple University, School of Communication &

Design

High School New Orleans Center for Creative Arts (NOCCA)